<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<LocalizedText>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MORA_PORRAS_TITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Juan Rafael Mora Porras</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MORA_PORRAS_SUBTITLE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>President of Costa Rica</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_LEADER_MORA_PORRAS_QUOTE" Language="en_US">
			<Text>The peoples who do not defend theirs, end up being tenants in their own country.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MORA_PORRAS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_1" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Juan Rafael Mora Porras was a Costa Rican politician to serve as the second President of the country from 1849 to 1860. Juan Rafael Mora Porras was born on 8 Fabruaby 1814 in San Jose. He belonged to one of the oldest families of the ruling oligarchy. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MORA_PORRAS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_2" Language="en_US">
			<Text>He was a prosperous coffee planter. His principal problem was rivalry for power with other oligarchical families. He used his office to favor economic activities of relatives and friends, enabling a small group to monopolize credit and trade and virtually dictating his reelection in 1853. This led to decline in his popularity and to doubts that he could complete his second term.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="LOC_PEDIA_LEADERS_PAGE_LEADER_MORA_PORRAS_CHAPTER_HISTORY_PARA_3" Language="en_US">
			<Text>Mora rallied the Costa Ricans and much of Central America in a war of resistance against the filibusterer William Walker. The conflict transformed Mora’s troubled rule into popular acclaim, but when he tried to extend his rule for a third term in 1859, his enemies and the generals removed him. When, in I860, he attempted to return to power at the head of an invading column, government forces under President José Maria Montealegre captured and executed him.</Text>
		</Row>
	</LocalizedText>

	<BaseGameText>
		<Row Tag="LOC_LOADING_INFO_LEADER_MORA_PORRAS">
			<Text>President Juan Rafael Mora Porras, you will lead Costa Rica through one of the most difficult time of the history of the country, and your people will emerge all the stronger for it. You will unite old nemesis against the same cause, and you will show  your leadership on these dark times.</Text>
		</Row>
	</BaseGameText>
</GameData>
